Mss.B.H142.1-3
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Account with Benjamin Franklin, Feb. 7, 1766 - Jan. 7, 1772; 13x7; Hall, David. Estate
    D. 1 leaf. (Located in box with letterbooks.) Mentions Mrs. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME95
  - Letter to Mrs. Hall, April 7, 1778; Strahan, William, 1715-1785
  - Letter to William Hall, Dec. 19, 1796; Leacock, Joseph
  - Letter to W[illia]m Hall, Dec. 30, 1800; Leacock, Joseph
  - Statement as to monies due him, [1807]
  - Letter to [William Hall], May 23, 1807; Leacock, Joseph
  - Notice of dissoluction of partnership, July 22, 1807; Hall & Sellers.
  - Letter to H. Weissenbach, Nov. 20, 1807; Hall, William
  - Memorial to the U.S. Congress, Jan. 10, 1809; Hall, William
  - Will, Feb. 1822; Hall, William
  - Epitaph for Mr. Lawrence Booze, n.d.
- Bound volumes, 4.0 4 Letterbooks: 1. June 21, 1750- Dec. 24, 1755 2. June 2, 1750- March 24, 1759 3. March 27, 1759-April 12, 1764 4. May 3, 1764-Nov. 16, 1767 Please use photocopy.; Hall, David, 1714-1772
  Series II. Bound volumes: 4 Letterbooks, 4 account books, 1 receipt book
  See separate, typed TOC (table of contents) in front of box.
  - Letterbook, 1750-1755, June 21,1750-Dec. 24,1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Feb. 2, 1750/1; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Refers to B.Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME10
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, Feb. 2, 1750/1; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Refers to Strahan.
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, June 2, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business.
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 2, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business.
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 23, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, July 13, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, July 13, 27, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Concerning B.Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME8
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, Aug. 18, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Philadelphia, Aug. 18, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business.
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, Sept. 27, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Sept. 27, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Refers to B.Franklin and John Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME9
    - Letter to William Strahan, Nov. 20, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business.
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, Nov. 20, 1750; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 28, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 3p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Orders books. Refers to B.Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME11
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, March 28, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, June, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, [ca.]. A.L. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 28, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L. 3p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business Orders books.
    - Letter to Adrian Watkins, Edinburgh, June 29, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Concerning Strahan.
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, June 29, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business.
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, July 6, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Orders books for Thomas Bond and others.
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, July 21, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, July 21, 22, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to Will[ia]m Strahan, Sept., 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      [ca.] A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business.
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Edinburgh, Sept. 7, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Mentions Strahan.
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, London, Sept. 7, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Refers to Strahan.
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Sept. 7, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Adrian Watkins, Nov. 23, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Orders books to be sent via John Franklin in Boston. FILM54-64 FRAME 92
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, London, Nov. 23, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Will[ia]m Strahan, Nov. 23, 1751; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 3p. Copy. Last part of letter lacking. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 21, 1752; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Concerning a glass for Sally Franklin. FILM54-64FRAME 91
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, March 21, June 13, 1752; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, Aug. 8, Sept. 1, 1752; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Aug. 8, 1752; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Sept. 1, 1752; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Copy. Misdated Nov. 1, 1752. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, Oct. 4, 1752; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Oct. 4, 1752; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Orders books. Business.
    - Letter to Adrian Watkins, Nov. 19, 1752; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, April 18, 1753; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, April 18, 1753; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, Nov., 1753; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, [before] A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Refers to Strahan.
    - Letter to William Strahan, Nov., 1753; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, [before] A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business.
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, Nov. 28, 1753; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Nov. 28, 1753; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Friendly letter. Asks favor for James Stevenson.
    - Letter to John Newberry & co., London, Dec. 8, 1753; B. Franklin and D. Hall (Firm)
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. FILM 54-64 FRAME 12
    - Letter to Adrian Watkins, Dec. 8, 1753; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, March 14, 1754; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 14, 1754; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Bloss & Johnson, April 20, 1754; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Aug. 7, 1754; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 3p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Order books. Business. Concerning B.Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME13
    - Letter to Job Johnson, Oct. 8, 1754; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Oct. 8, 1754; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Friendly letter. Trouble with French on the frontier.
    - Letter to Adrian Watkins, Dec. 18, 1754; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business.
    - Letter to Job Johnson, Dec.18, Jan. 3, 1754, 175[5]; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Dec. 18, Jan. 3, 1754, 175[5]; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Orders books. Concerning B.Franklin and Hunter as postmaster-generals.
    - Letter to Job Johnson, London, April 7, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, April 7, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Job Johnson, May 1, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, May 1, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, London, July 10, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, London, Oct. 7, 9, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, London, Oct. 25, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Job Johnson, London, Nov. 25, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Nov. 25, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Concerning the French and Indian war.
    - Letter to Job Johnson, Dec. 17, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Dec. 17, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. Franklin busy in the frontier. FILM54-64 FRAME 16
    - Letter to William Strahan, Dec. 24, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see D. Hall Letterbook, 1750-1759.) Business. B.Franklin busy in the frontier. FILM54-64 FRAME17
  - Letterbook, 1750-1759, June 2, 1750-March 24, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, London, Aug. 28, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L.S. with initials. 2p. Orders fonts of type.
    - Letter to Job Johnson, London, Oct. 7, 1755; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Copy. Business.
    - Letter to Oliver Hart, Charles Town, S.C., Oct. 19, 1755; Franklin and Hall
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME15
    - Letter to Job Johnson, March 3, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 3, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. War in America.
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 4, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Orders type.
    - Letter to James Davis, North Carolina, March 17, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Concerning B.Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME18
    - Letter to William Strahan, April 23, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Friendly letter.
    - Letter to James Davis, April 24, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 16, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 3p. Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 26, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business.
    - Letter to Curtis Brett & Co., Jamaica, Aug. 31, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alexander Davidson, Jamaica, Sept. 20, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to R. Williamson, Liverpool, Sept. 23, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Refers to B.Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME19
    - Letter to Job Johnson, London, Sept. 23, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Mentions Strahan.
    - Letter to William Strahan, Sept. 23, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Nov. 3, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Nov. 8, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Nov. 30, 1756; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Jan. 10, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to R. Williamson, Liverpool, Jan. 12, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Refers to B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME20
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Jan. 12, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Jan. 30, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Orders books and paper.
    - Letter to William Strahan, Feb. 14, 21, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. with initials. 3p. Business. Concerning B.Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME21
    - Letter to William Strahan, April 4, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to [Franklin and Hall], May 26, 1757; Hunter, James
      Fredericksburg, L. Copy. 1p. Business. In letter from Hall to Franklin; July 4, 1757. FILM54-64 FRAME22
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, London, July 4, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Enc. Business. Printed: Labaree, Papers, VII, 237-8. In letter is letter from James Hunter to Franklin and Hall; May 26, 1757. FILM54-64 FRAME22
    - Letter to Rivington & Fletcher, London, July 4, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, London, July 4, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Sept. 13, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Refers to Strahan.
    - Letter to William Strahan, Sept. 13, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 3p. Business. Orders books. News of the war. Mentions Benjamin and William Franklin.
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Sept. 14, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Printed: Labaree, Papers, vol. VII, 254. Film 54-64 Frame 24.
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Oct. 19, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Printed: Labaree, Papers, vol. VII, 270. FILM54-64 FRAME25
    - Letter to William Strahan, Oct. 19, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Nov. 20, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Printed: Labaree, Papers, vol. VII, 272. FILM54-64 FRAME26
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Nov. 20, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Nov. 20, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Dec. 22, 1757; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. with initials. 1p. Business.
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Jan. 6, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Printed: Labaree, Papers, vol. VII, 357-8. FILM54-64 FRAME27
    - Letter to William Strahan, Jan. 6, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Feb. 6, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. printed: Labaree, Papers, vol. VII, 371. FILM54-64 FRAME28
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Feb. 6, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Feb. 20, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Printed: Labaree, Papers,vol. VII, 384. FILM54-64 FRAME29
    - Letter to William Strahan, Feb. 20, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Franklin, April 24, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      [Philadelphia, D. 1p. Note of letter, but not copy of letter. FILM54-family FRAME 29
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, April 24, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, April 24, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Refers to Strahan. FILM54-64 FRAME31
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, April 24, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to James Rivington, London, April 24, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, April 24, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Orders him to pay B. Franklin £100. FILM54-64 FRAME30
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, May 29, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to James Rivington, May 29, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, May 29, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, July 22, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, July 22, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Refers to Strahan. FILM54-64 FRAME32
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, July 22, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Refers to Strahan.
    - Letter to James Rivington, July 22, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Nov. 20, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME33
    - Letter to Rivington & Fletcher, London, Nov. 20, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Nov. 20, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Nov. 26, 1758; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Jan. 18, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Jan. 18, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Refers to Strahan. FILM54-64 FRAME34
    - Letter to James Rivington, Jan. 18, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Feb. 24, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Feb. 24, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Feb. 27, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Will address his letters to Peter Collinson. FILM54-64 FRAME 35
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 1, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, March 24 - April 9, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Addressed to Peter Collinson. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME36
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, March 24, April 9, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Rivington & Fletcher, March 24, April 9, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 24, April 9, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
  - Letterbook, 1759-1764, March 27, 1759-April 12, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, March 27, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Orders books.
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 18, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Refers to B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME38
    - Letter to Rivington & Fletcher, June 18, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business.
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, June 18, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Forwards bill of exchange.
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, June 18, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Mentions Strahan. FILM54-64 FRAME37
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Aug., 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Refers to W. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME39
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Edinburgh, Aug. 9, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business letter concerning Robert Smith.
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Aug. 9, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Rivington & Fletcher, Aug. 9, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business.
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Aug. 9, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to B[enjamin] Franklin, Aug. 21, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business letter. FILM54-64 FRAME 40
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Aug. 21, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Rivington & Fletcher, Aug. 21, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. with initials, 1p. Business.
    - Letter to B[enjamin] Franklin, Dec. 15, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Friendly letter. Mentions W. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME41
    - Letter to Rivington & Fletcher, Dec. 15, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Mentions Strahan.
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Dec. 15, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Dec. 15, 1759; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, March 5, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME42
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, March 5, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, March 5, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, March 5, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, March 6, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, March 31, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME 43
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, March 31, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, March 31, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, April 18, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME44
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, April 18, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, April 18, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Asks a favor.
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, April 20, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Friendly letter. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME45
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, April 20, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, April 20, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, July 2, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Refers to R. Smith
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, July 2, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME46
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, July 2, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, July 2, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter. Orders books.
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Aug. 26, 31, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter. Business. Mentions Mrs. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME 47
    - Letter to David Barclay & Sons, Aug. 31, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Aug. 31, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Concerning B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME48
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Sept. 27, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Sept. 27, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Oct. 6, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Friendly letter. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME49
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Oct. 6, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Oct. 22, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Nov. 15, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Personal matters. Refers to R. Smith.
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Nov.15, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Friendly letter.
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Dec. 6, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Personal matters.
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, Dec. 6, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Dec. 22, 1760; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Refers to Rivington.
    - Letter to [William Strahan], Dec. 22, 1760 - Jan. 26, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L. 6p. Enc. wanting. Business. Orders Franklin's works on electricity. Orders books for Library Company and others. including Rivington. FILM54-64 FRAME50
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, Feb. 9, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Feb. 9, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Concerning Rivington.
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, Feb. 21, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME52